Lloyd Wright papers LSC.1561
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 1: Files
  - Project Files
    - Heifetz, Jascha - Studio & remodel, Project No. 177
      - Construction contractor, Project No. 177 (Box 37, Folder 2)
      - Cost estimates & recapitulations, Project No. 177 (Box 37, Folder 3)
      - Notes & cuts, Project No. 177 (Box 37, Folder 4)
      - Contractor's certificates, Project No. 177 (Box 37, Folder 5)
      - Construction correspondence, Project No. 177 (Box 37, Folder 6)
      - Payroll record, Project No. 177 (Box 37, Folder 7)
      - Permits & notice of completion, Project No. 177 (Box 37, Folder 8)
      - Engineering design, Project No. 177 (Box 37, Folder 9)
      - Sub-contractors' agreements, Project No. 177 (Box 37, Folder 10)
      - Sub-contractors' certificates, Project No. 177 (Box 37, Folder 11)
      - Bids - construction, Project No. 177 (Box 37, Folder 12)
      - Contractor / owner's agreement for guest room & new bath, Project No. 177 (Box 37, Folder 13)
      - Specifications - sub-contractors, Project No. 177 (Box 37, Folder 14)
      - Architect's certificates, Project No. 177 (Box 37, Folder 15)
      - Plan receipts & records, Project No. 177 (Box 37, Folder 16)
      - Construction (Hase), Project No. 177 (Box 37, Folder 17)
      - Material bills & vouchers - job notes included, Project No. 177 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Henrichs, Henry F. - Press building
      - General, Project No. 108 (Box 34, Folder 12)
      - Miscellaneous, Project No. 108 (Box 34, Folder 13)
      - Bills, agreements, etc., Project No. 108 (Box 35, Folder 1)
      - Air conditioning, Project No. 108 (Box 35, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, Project No. 108 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Henry, Burns - Residence, Project No. 352
      - Specifications (Box 91, Folder 14)
      - Client - correspondence (Box 91, Folder 15)
      - Client - notes & cuts (Box 91, Folder 16)
      - Brochures (Box 91, Folder 17)
      - Program surveys (Box 91, Folder 18)
      - Land surveys (Box 91, Folder 19)
      - Architect / owner agreement (Box 91, Folder 20)
      - Architect - certificates (Box 91, Folder 21)
      - Cost estimates (Box 91, Folder 22)
      - Quantity estimates (Box 91, Folder 23)
      - Estimates - engineering (1 of 2) (Box 91, Folder 24)
      - Estimates - engineering (2 of 2) (Box 91, Folder 25)
      - General contractors - proposals (Box 91, Folder 26)
      - Sub-contractors (Box 91, Folder 27)
      - Specifications (1 of 2) (Box 91, Folder 28)
      - Specifications (2 of 2) (Box 91, Folder 29)
      - Plan checks & records (Box 91, Folder 30)
      - Construction - job notes (Box 91, Folder 31)
    - Hollywood Bowl - Shells 1 & 2
      - Properties survey for "Theatre Arts Alliance" tract, Project No. 11 (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Contracts & correspondence - 1928, Project No. 11 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Bowl & tract & entrance model studies - plans & sketches, Project No. 11 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - Bowl shell costs - 1928, Project No. 11 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - Subcontracts - 1928, Project No. 11 (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Specifications - 1928, Project No. 11 (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - Shell cost data - 1928, Project No. 11 (Box 22, Folder 8)
      - Shell correspondence - 1928, Project No. 11 (Box 22, Folder 9)
      - Structural calculations & details for 1928 shell, Project No. 11 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Holmby Park - Art display
      - General, Project No. 214 (Box 62, Folder 19)
    - Honeycutt, Rev. - Residence & landscaping
      - Client correspondence & notes, Project No. 231 (Box 63, Folder 4)
      - Architect's agreements & certificates, Project No. 231 (Box 63, Folder 5)
      - Estimates - quantity survey, Project No. 231 (Box 63, Folder 6)
      - Estimates - cost, Project No. 231 (Box 63, Folder 7)
      - Estimates - engineering, Project No. 231 (Box 63, Folder 8)
      - Specifications - general, Project No. 231 (Box 63, Folder 9)
      - Plan checks & records, Project No. 231 (Box 63, Folder 10)
      - Construction, Project No. 231 (Box 63, Folder 11)
      - Desk folder, Project No. 231 (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Housing & Rural Rehabilitation
      - Folder 1 of 3 (Box 42, Folder 9)
      - Folder 2 of 3 (Box 43, Folder 1)
      - Folder 3 of 3 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Howard, Frank - Remodel & addition, Project No. 238
      - Construction - John V. Greathead, contractor (Box 64, Folder 14)
      - Final release on job (Box 64, Folder 15)
    - Howard, Frank - Remodel & additions to pool & ramada, Project No. 265
      - Desk folder (Box 64, Folder 16)
      - Land survey (Box 64, Folder 17)
      - Estimates (Box 64, Folder 18)
      - Architect's certificates (Box 64, Folder 19)
      - Plan checks & records (Box 64, Folder 20)
      - Client notes (Box 64, Folder 21)
      - Construction (Box 64, Folder 22)
      - Job notes (Box 64, Folder 23)
      - Construction - bids (Box 64, Folder 24)
      - Court data (Box 64, Folder 25)
      - General (Box 65, Folder 30)
    - Howard, Frank - Residence & addition, Project No. 238
      - Miscellaneous (Box 64, Folder 1)
      - Notes & correspondence (Box 64, Folder 2)
      - Land survey (Box 64, Folder 3)
      - Architect's agreements & certificates (Box 64, Folder 4)
      - Estimates (Box 64, Folder 5)
      - Plan checks & records (Box 64, Folder 6)
      - Construction - daily journal, job notes & payroll (Box 64, Folder 7)
      - Construction - ramadas (Box 64, Folder 8)
      - Construction - Douglas / Roesch (Box 64, Folder 9)
      - Construction - planting contract (Box 64, Folder 10)
      - Construction - Melrose carpenter shop (Box 64, Folder 11)
      - Construction - bids (Box 64, Folder 12)
      - Construction - contractors (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - Howe, Herbert - Residence
      - Specifications & contracts, Project No. 20 (Box 22, Folder 19)
      - Bills, Project No. 20 (Box 22, Folder 20)
      - Correspondence, Project No. 20 (Box 22, Folder 21)
      - General, Project No. 20 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Howland, Jobyna - Residence
      - General, Project No. 74 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Hunt, Mrs. S.M.B. - Plant list
      - unspecified, Project No. 38C (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Huntington Portal - Hotel, apartments, motel, marina, esplanade, Project No. 297
      - Drawings (Box 74, Folder 1)
      - Sunset Bay - preliminaries & supervision journal (Box 74, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence (Box 74, Folder 3)
      - Sunset Bay - feasibility study (Box 74, Folder 4)
      - Notes (Box 74, Folder 5)
      - Client notes (Box 74, Folder 6)
      - Client's data - required for preliminary studies (Box 74, Folder 7)
      - Client - notes for Lee Martin (Box 74, Folder 8)
      - Client - accommodations for income (Box 74, Folder 9)
      - Architect / owner agreement (Box 74, Folder 10)
      - Architect's certificates (Box 74, Folder 11)
      - Architect's studies (Box 74, Folder 12)
      - Land survey (Box 74, Folder 13)
      - Lincoln Fidelity Corp - cost data (Box 74, Folder 14)
      - Estimates (Box 74, Folder 15)
      - Plan checks & records (Box 74, Folder 16)
    - Institute of Mentalphysics - Caravansary, & administration building & site plan, Project No. 158
      - Correspondence, Project No. 158 (Box 47, Folder 1)
      - General notes (folder 1 of 2), Project No. 158 (Box 47, Folder 2)
      - General notes (folder 2 of 2), Project No. 158 (Box 47, Folder 3)
      - Brochures, Project No. 158 (Box 47, Folder 4)
      - Architectural studies, Project No. 158 (Box 47, Folder 5)
      - Photos & brochures, Project No. 158 (Box 47, Folder 6)
      - Client notes, Project No. 158 (Box 47, Folder 7)
      - Notes, Project No. 158 (Box 47, Folder 8)
      - Land survey, Project No. 158 (Box 47, Folder 9)
      - Duplicates, obsoletes, etc., Project No. 158 (Box 47, Folder 10)
      - Notice of completion, Project No. 158 (Box 47, Folder 11)
      - Notes, Project No. 158 (Box 47, Folder 12)
      - Contracts - unsigned, Project No. 158 (Box 47, Folder 13)
      - Estimates (folder 1 of 2), Project No. 158 (Box 47, Folder 14)
      - Estimates (folder 2 of 2), Project No. 158 (Box 47, Folder 15)
      - Agreements, Project No. 158 (Box 47, Folder 16)
      - Certificates, Project No. 158 (Box 47, Folder 17)
      - Specifications, Project No. 158 (Box 47, Folder 18)
      - Plan checks & records, Project No. 158 (Box 47, Folder 19)
      - Supervision journal, Project No. 158 (Box 47, Folder 20)
      - Sub-contractor's certificates (folder 1 of 3), Project No. 158 (Box 47, Folder 21)
      - Sub-contractor's certificates (folder 2 of 3), Project No. 158 (Box 47, Folder 22)
      - Sub-contractor's certificates (folder 3 of 3), Project No. 158 (Box 47, Folder 23)
      - Lathing - plastering, Project No. 158 (Box 47, Folder 24)
      - Abar journal notes - retrial, Project No. 158 (Box 47, Folder 25)
      - Contractor's agreements, Project No. 158 (Box 47, Folder 26)
      - Contractor's correspondence, Project No. 158 (Box 47, Folder 27)
      - Construction, Project No. 158 (Box 48, Folder 1)
      - Construction bids, Project No. 158 (Box 48, Folder 2)
      - Material bills & vouchers, Project No. 158 (Box 48, Folder 3)
      - Client correspondence, Project No. 158 (Box 48, Folder 4)
      - Client notes & cuts, Project No. 158 (Box 48, Folder 5)
      - Estimates - quantity survey, Project No. 158 (Box 48, Folder 6)
      - Estimates - cost estimates, Project No. 158 (Box 48, Folder 7)
      - Estimates - trip cost estimates, Project No. 158 (Box 48, Folder 8)
      - Estimates - engineering calculations, Project No. 158 (Box 48, Folder 9)
      - Architect agreements, Project No. 158 (Box 48, Folder 10)
      - Architect certificates, Project No. 158 (Box 48, Folder 11)
      - Specifications - general, Project No. 158 (Box 48, Folder 12)
      - Specifications - sub-contractors, Project No. 158 (Box 48, Folder 13)
      - Plan checks & records, Project No. 158 (Box 48, Folder 14)
      - Construction - payroll records, Project No. 158 (Box 48, Folder 15)
      - Construction - contractors, Project No. 158 (Box 48, Folder 16)
      - Construction - sub-contractors, Project No. 158 (Box 48, Folder 17)
      - Construction - bids, Project No. 158 (Box 48, Folder 18)
      - Sub-contractors agreements (folder 1 of 3), Project No. 158 (Box 48, Folder 19)
      - Sub-contractors agreements (folder 2 of 3), Project No. 158 (Box 48, Folder 20)
      - Sub-contractors agreements (folder 3 of 3), Project No. 158 (Box 48, Folder 21)
    - Institute of Mentalphysics - Cafeteria & cottages
      - Client notes (folder 1 of 2), Project No. 240 (Box 46, Folder 16)
      - Client notes (folder 2 of 2), Project No. 240 (Box 46, Folder 17)
      - Housing units - general, Project No. 240 (Box 48, Folder 22)
      - Housing units - kitchen, Project No. 240 (Box 48, Folder 23)
      - Photographs - Jan. 16, 1956, Project No. 240 (Box 48, Folder 24)
      - Photographs - March 1, 1956, Project No. 240 (Box 48, Folder 25)
      - Photographs - April 24, 1956, Project No. 240 (Box 48, Folder 26)
      - Photographs - May 14, 1956, Project No. 240 (Box 48, Folder 27)
      - Photographs - May 16, 1956, Project No. 240 (Box 48, Folder 28)
      - Photographs - May 22, 1956, Project No. 240 (Box 48, Folder 29)
      - Photographs - May 25, 1956, Project No. 240 (Box 48, Folder 30)
      - Photographs - Aug. 23, 1956, Project No. 240 (Box 48, Folder 31)
      - Site plan, Project No. 240 (Box 48, Folder 32)
      - Joshua Monument Desert Journal (April 5, 1956), Project No. 240 (Box 48, Folder 33)
      - Land survey, Project No. 240 (Box 48, Folder 34)
      - Architect - agreements, Project No. 240 (Box 48, Folder 35)
      - Architect - certificates, Project No. 240 (Box 48, Folder 36)
      - Travel notes, Project No. 240 (Box 48, Folder 37)
      - Estimates - quantities, Project No. 240 (Box 48, Folder 38)
      - Estimates - planting, Project No. 240 (Box 48, Folder 39)
      - Estimates - grading, Project No. 240 (Box 48, Folder 40)
      - Estimates - hardware, Project No. 240 (Box 48, Folder 41)
      - Estimates - electrical, Project No. 240 (Box 48, Folder 42)
      - Estimates - blocks, Project No. 240 (Box 48, Folder 43)
      - Estimates - cost data - electrical, Project No. 240 (Box 48, Folder 44)
      - Estimates - sash & door schedule, Project No. 240 (Box 48, Folder 45)
      - Estimates - steel data, Project No. 240 (Box 48, Folder 46)
      - Estimates (folder 1 of 2), Project No. 240 (Box 49, Folder 1)
      - Estimates (folder 2 of 2), Project No. 240 (Box 49, Folder 2)
      - Duplex & triplex - specifications, Project No. 240 (Box 49, Folder 3)
      - Cafeteria - specifications (folder 1 of 2), Project No. 240 (Box 49, Folder 4)
      - Cafeteria - specifications (folder 2 of 2), Project No. 240 (Box 49, Folder 5)
      - Sub - contractors' specifications - general, Project No. 240 (Box 49, Folder 6)
      - Cafeteria - utilities, Project No. 240 (Box 49, Folder 7)
      - Utility installation, Project No. 240 (Box 49, Folder 8)
      - Utilities, Project No. 240 (Box 49, Folder 9)
      - Specifications, Project No. 240 (Box 49, Folder 10)
      - Plan checks & records, Project No. 240 (Box 49, Folder 11)
      - Paint data, Project No. 240 (Box 49, Folder 12)
      - General bids, Project No. 240 (Box 49, Folder 13)
      - Construction, Project No. 240 (Box 49, Folder 14)
      - Construction / owner agreement, Project No. 240 (Box 49, Folder 15)
      - Construction certificates, Project No. 240 (Box 49, Folder 16)
      - Vouchers, Project No. 240 (Box 49, Folder 17)
      - Construction, Project No. 240 (Box 49, Folder 18)
      - Contractors - miscellaneous, Project No. 240 (Box 49, Folder 19)
      - Sub-contractors agreements - construction, Project No. 240 (Box 50, Folder 1)
      - Sub-contractors certificates, Project No. 240 (Box 50, Folder 2)
      - Sub-contractors - correspondence, Project No. 240 (Box 50, Folder 3)
      - Simsarian - plumbing, Project No. 240 (Box 50, Folder 4)
      - Bids - reexcavation, Project No. 240 (Box 50, Folder 5)
      - Bids - electrical, Project No. 240 (Box 50, Folder 6)
      - Supervision journal, Project No. 240 (Box 50, Folder 7)
      - Construction job notes, Project No. 240 (Box 50, Folder 8)
      - Construction applications, Project No. 240 (Box 50, Folder 9)
      - San Bernadino County Building Department - data, Project No. 240 (Box 50, Folder 10)
      - Notice of completion, Project No. 240 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Institute of Mentalphysics - Preceptory & sanctuary, Project No. 253
      - Model, Project No. 253 (Box 50, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence, Project No. 253 (Box 50, Folder 13)
      - Sound equipment, Project No. 253 (Box 50, Folder 14)
      - Design studies, Project No. 253 (Box 50, Folder 15)
      - Clients - program outline, Project No. 253 (Box 50, Folder 16)
      - Client notes - science of soil mechanics, Project No. 253 (Box 50, Folder 17)
      - Architect's agreements, Project No. 253 (Box 50, Folder 18)
      - Architect's certificates, Project No. 253 (Box 50, Folder 19)
      - Architect - trips, Project No. 253 (Box 50, Folder 20)
      - Cost estimates, Project No. 253 (Box 50, Folder 21)
      - Estimates - general, Project No. 253 (Box 50, Folder 22)
      - Estimates - electrical & plumbing, Project No. 253 (Box 50, Folder 23)
      - Estimates - bids, Project No. 253 (Box 50, Folder 24)
      - Estimates - quantity, Project No. 253 (Box 50, Folder 25)
      - Estimates - quantity - lumber, Project No. 253 (Box 50, Folder 26)
      - Calculation of load - electrical, Project No. 253 (Box 50, Folder 27)
      - Estimates - engineering, Project No. 253 (Box 50, Folder 28)
      - Estimates - preliminary - engineering calculations, Project No. 253 (Box 50, Folder 29)
      - Specification, Project No. 253 (Box 50, Folder 30)
      - Specifications - general, Project No. 253 (Box 50, Folder 31)
      - Plan checks & records, Project No. 253 (Box 50, Folder 32)
      - Sub-contractors' agreements, Project No. 253 (Box 50, Folder 33)
      - Sub-contractors' correspondence, Project No. 253 (Box 50, Folder 34)
      - Construction bids, Project No. 253 (Box 50, Folder 35)
      - Sub-bids, Project No. 253 (Box 50, Folder 36)
      - Construction bids - engineering, Project No. 253 (Box 50, Folder 37)
      - Construction - Peckman, Project No. 253 (Box 50, Folder 38)
      - Construction - Clerk of the work, Project No. 253 (Box 50, Folder 39)
      - Clerk of the work - applications, Project No. 253 (Box 50, Folder 40)
      - C.L. Cunningham - credit rating & general data, Project No. 253 (Box 50, Folder 41)
      - Construction permit data, Project No. 253 (Box 50, Folder 42)
      - Construction - job notes & supervisor's journal, Project No. 158 (Box 51, Folder 1)
      - Desk folder, Project No. 158 (Box 51, Folder 2)
      - Construction - low bids, Project No. 158 (Box 51, Folder 3)
      - Construction - high bids, Project No. 158 (Box 51, Folder 4)
      - Specifications, Project No. 158 (Box 51, Folder 5)
      - Miscellaneous, Project No. 158 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Jacobi, Jerome - Residence remodel [Storer house], Project No. 343
      - Correspondence (Box 89, Folder 15)
      - Architect/ owner contract (Box 89, Folder 16)
      - Time cards (Box 89, Folder 17)
      - Architect reimbursements (Box 89, Folder 18)
      - Architect - certificates (Box 89, Folder 19)
      - Planning notes (Box 89, Folder 20)
      - Sheet metal - bids (Box 89, Folder 21)
      - Ceramic tile (Box 89, Folder 22)
      - Electrical (Box 89, Folder 23)
      - Items to be done (Box 89, Folder 24)
      - Construction notes (Box 89, Folder 25)
      - Original folder (Box 89, Folder 26)
      - Furniture notes (Box 89, Folder 27)
      - Current work - job file (Box 89, Folder 28)
      - Construction - job notes (Box 89, Folder 29)
      - New work - restoration (Box 89, Folder 30)
      - Roofing - new bids (Box 89, Folder 31)
      - Construction - printing lists (Box 89, Folder 32)
      - Construction - swimming pools (Box 89, Folder 33)
      - Unpaid bills (Box 89, Folder 34)
      - Miscellaneous bills - paid (Box 89, Folder 35)
      - Painting estimates (Box 89, Folder 36)
      - Specifications - air conditioning (Box 89, Folder 37)
      - Heating (Box 89, Folder 38)
      - Sandblasting (Box 89, Folder 39)
      - Roofing bids (Box 89, Folder 40)
      - Payment record - Pete Purens (Box 89, Folder 41)
      - Carpenter work - time records (Box 89, Folder 42)
      - Architect fee billings & reimbursements (Box 89, Folder 43)
      - Architect - certificates (Box 90, Folder 1)
      - Estimates (Box 90, Folder 2)
      - Plan checks & records (Box 90, Folder 3)
      - Specifications - swimming pool (Box 90, Folder 3)
      - Job schedule (Box 90, Folder 5)
      - Construction - garage door & gates - new bids (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - Jester, Ralph - Residence
      - Cost estimates, Project No. 187 (Box 56, Folder 46)
      - Engineering data, Project No. 187 (Box 56, Folder 47)
      - General specifications, Project No. 187 (Box 56, Folder 48)
      - Plan checks & records, Project No. 187 (Box 56, Folder 49)
      - Architect's certificates, Project No. 187 (Box 56, Folder 50)
      - Client notes & cuts, Project No. 187 (Box 56, Folder 51)
      - Quantity surveys, Project No. 187 (Box 56, Folder 52)
    - Johnson, Beverly - Residence, Project No. 309
      - Specifications - general (1 of 3) (Box 76, Folder 16)
      - Specifications (2 of 3) (Box 76, Folder 17)
      - Specifications (3 of 3) (Box 76, Folder 18)
      - Labor release (Box 77, Folder 1)
      - Applications (Box 77, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence (Box 77, Folder 3)
      - Job notes (Box 77, Folder 4)
      - Client - correspondence (Box 77, Folder 5)
      - Construction - photos (Box 77, Folder 6)
      - Client - notes (Box 77, Folder 7)
      - Construction - landscaping & grading (Box 77, Folder 8)
      - Estimates - engineering & construction (Box 77, Folder 9)
      - Contractor / owner agreements (Box 77, Folder 10)
      - Contractor's correspondence (Box 77, Folder 11)
      - Architect / owner agreements (Box 77, Folder 12)
      - Architect's certificates (Box 77, Folder 13)
      - Construction - engineering bills (Box 77, Folder 14)
      - Land surveys (Box 77, Folder 15)
      - Land surveys - maps (Box 77, Folder 16)
      - Plan checks & records (Box 77, Folder 17)
      - Cost estimates (Box 77, Folder 18)
      - Cost estimates for building reports (Box 77, Folder 19)
      - Estimates - quantity (Box 77, Folder 20)
      - Construction - bids (Box 77, Folder 21)
      - Grading & landscaping (Box 77, Folder 22)
      - Summation of building costs (Box 77, Folder 23)
      - Termination of architectural services (Box 77, Folder 24)
      - 16th statement of account (Box 77, Folder 25)
      - 15th statement of account (Box 77, Folder 26)
      - 14th statement of account (Box 77, Folder 27)
      - 13th statement of account (Box 77, Folder 28)
      - 12th statement of account (Box 77, Folder 29)
      - 11th statement of account (Box 77, Folder 30)
      - 10th statement of account (Box 77, Folder 31)
      - 9th statement of account (Box 77, Folder 32)
      - 8th statement of account (Box 77, Folder 33)
      - 7th statement of account (Box 77, Folder 34)
      - 6th statement of account (Box 77, Folder 35)
      - 5th statement of account (Box 77, Folder 36)
      - 4th statement of account (Box 77, Folder 37)
      - 1st - 2nd - 3rd statement of account (Box 77, Folder 38)
      - Extras re statements 1-5 (Box 77, Folder 39)
      - Johnson building account statements (Box 77, Folder 40)
      - Contractor - bids (Box 78, Folder 1)
      - Tile contract (Box 78, Folder 2)
      - Painting contracts (Box 78, Folder 3)
      - Stone contract (Box 78, Folder 4)
      - Wood contract (Box 78, Folder 5)
      - Deck contract (Box 78, Folder 6)
      - Duplicate contracts (Box 78, Folder 7)
      - Hardware lists (Box 78, Folder 8)
      - Wood door / window schedule (Box 78, Folder 9)
      - Sheet metal contract (Box 78, Folder 10)
      - Plastering contract (Box 78, Folder 11)
      - Lumber (Box 78, Folder 12)
      - Construction - miscellaneous (Box 78, Folder 13)
      - Construction (Box 78, Folder 14)
      - Correspondence (Box 78, Folder 15)
      - Construction - certificates (1 of 4) (Box 78, Folder 16)
      - Construction - certificates (2 of 4) (Box 78, Folder 17)
      - Construction - certificates (3 of 4) (Box 78, Folder 18)
      - Construction - certificates (4 of 4) (Box 78, Folder 19)
    - Jones, Carol - Furniture
      - General, Project No. 53 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Jones, Frank - Residence
      - General, Project No. 143 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Jones, Mr. & Mrs. Felix - Residence
      - Bids & contracts, Project No. 105 (Box 33, Folder 13)
      - General, Project No. 105 (Box 34, Folder 1)
      - Sub-bids, Project No. 105 (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence & miscellaneous, Project No. 105 (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - Bills & receipts, Project No. 105 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Joshua Tree, National Park - Monument, Project No. 245
      - General (Box 65, Folder 17)
    - Jowdy, Moudary - Residence remodel
      - Agreements & certificates (Box 80, Folder 1)
      - Specifications - general (Box 80, Folder 2)
      - Estimates (Box 80, Folder 3)
      - Plan checks & records (Box 80, Folder 4)
      - Job notes (Box 80, Folder 5)
      - Construction (Box 80, Folder 6)
      - Client correspondence (Box 80, Folder 7)
      - Job notes (Box 80, Folder 8)
      - Desk folder (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Kanin, Michael - Apartment remodel, Project No. 286
      - Desk folder (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - Kanin, Sadie - Residence